Feast your eyes on that rat, would ya?
Dumb nation! Woo!
This bastard must have
died right quick, like.
Fell off that cliff, I'll warrant.
Courage wheels slipped in the mud.
They weren't hurting for coin, if
these fine clothes tell it true.
Dario, the lady is dead,
but the baby with her.
It's still alive, I can hear it.
She must have protected it
with her body. Leave it be.
Soon enough it'll be dead.
What are you doing?
You've got eyes, ain't you, woman?
I'm appropriating his jewellery, huh?
What have we here?
Evil-looking thing, ain't it?
Well, fetch me nothing.
Hey!
Lend a hand!
Help me yank out his pearly teeth!
They'll fetch a pretty copper!
Providence sends me aid in the
guise of a man. Many thanks.
My wife.
My wife and son.
Tell me, do they live?
I hate to say it, but your wife, Saint's
Preserver, has gone on to a heavenly rest.
But the baby is alive and well.
Fate is...
most cruel.
My name is George Joestar.
You have saved my life this cursed night.
Quickly tell me your name that I may
remember before my senses fail me.
This peacock thinks I'm here
out of the goodness of me heart.
Little does he know.
Guess I'll oblige him.
Doriel Brando, your lordship.
Sir, I swear to you, the Joestar family
will honor the debt we have incurred.
Ah, there's a good boy.
Father, I'm off!
Then fare thee well,
Jojo. Let's go, Danny.
T .O.
Mind your father.
Damn your eyes, you
lazy boy. Are you deaf?
What do you want, father? Medicine?
You idiot.
Their snake oil does me no good.
Get out of here.
And don't come back until
you've found me some booze.
Your manners are dreadful.
Forgive me, father.
Checkmate.
Take it.
Don't feel so smart now, do you, Welp?
Oh, let me guess, Serena, your daddy
bought you this doll, didn't he?
It's fancy.
Being a quack must pay him real nice.
I know.
What do you say we peel off
this fancy-looking dress, huh?
And see if they made her with all
the real girl bits underneath.
Me.
Oh my god!
Arena's a crybaby!
That's enough!
Give it back to her right now!
Who's this guy?
You some friend of Arena's?
I've never met her, but I'll
fight for her all the same!
Who is this idiot getting in a
fight for a girl he don't even know?
Looks like somebody It
was nothing but chalk.
Look at him there on the ground.
Are you going to cry?
Some knight in shining
armor you turned out to be.
Huh?
This little panty waist
is the Joestar kid.
Now that I know you're some rich
guy's son, we're just getting started.
You can't buy your way out of this.
Get him some more.
Listen, dear.
I am not long for this world.
When I die, you get yourself to the
Joestar mansion along with this letter.
The fool thinks he owes me.
This is your ticket to greatness.
It's your only chance, Dio.
Go out there and take this
useless world for all you can get.
Crawl on back to your damn manor,
little Lord Fauntleroy. Let's go.
You okay?
Just leave me alone!
I'll be fine!
I did not take a beating
just now for your sake!
So whatever you're thinking, stop it!
All I want is to conduct
myself as a gentleman.
I spotted a damsel in distress.
A true gentleman has no fear.
He'll fight for those who can't.
Even knowing it's a fight he has no
chance of winning, he enters the fray.
Someday, I'll have the strength to win.
Devil that you were, you drove
mother to an early grave.
I'm glad you're dead.
May you burn for your sins.
The riches that eluded your grasp,
I will claim them in excess.
You lacked the cunning to take
what you wanted, but I'll prevail.
This Joestar shall be the key.
Now burn!
I will claim what is rightfully mine.
Jonathan Joestar.
This is the tale of two young men,
their destinies bound to intersect,
and the stone mask that
changes their fates forever.
Who is he?
You must be Dio Brando, right?
And you're Jonathan, heir
to the Joestars. Yes.
Please, call me Jojo.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Danny!
That's Danny.
He's my dog as well as
my steadfast companion.
Don't worry.
He knows better than to nip at strangers.
What was that for?
How dare you!
So this is the brat I must usurp.
Where's his heart on his sleeve?
He's quick to anger.
This pampered fool is no match
for the likes of Dio Brando.
Fighting already?
I would know what this is about.
Sorry.
The dog jumped at me, and
in my haste, I struck it.
Welcome to the manor.
Consider yourself a part
of the family. Everyone.
I would have died in the crash that claimed
my wife were it not for Dio's father.
You will treat him as
you would my own son.
Very well, your lordship.
This is your home now, Dio.
Please avail yourself of all its comforts.
Thank you, sir, for taking
in this poor unfortunate.
Jojo has lost his mother as well.
And you're the same age.
You'll be thick as thieves soon, Jojo.
Dio didn't mean to hurt Dany.
Right.
It stands to reason, father.
If a strange dog jumped at
me, I'd be surprised too.
I wish his apology had been more sincere,
but as we'll be living here together,
I'll do my utmost to be friendly.
This way, Dio.
I'll show you your chamber.
Yes, sir.
You're hurting me!
Please let go!
Watch your hands.
No one's allowed to touch my
things without my permission.
What?
Next time you reach for what's
mine with this paw, I'll break it.
I was only trying to help.
I will have a servant
carry them up for me.
Listen, I may be a guest within your
house, but I am not to be trifled with.
In all things that I do, I am number one.
Look down your nose at
me and you'll regret it.
But Dio, I want for us to be friends.
And another thing, I hate all mongrels.
They don't scare me.
I just despise how they
fawn over the unworthy.
So keep that mangy mutt of yours
well away from me, Joestar.
Dio, what's keeping you? Hurry along.
Yes, sir.
With Dio's sudden arrival, Jojo's
carefree life spiraled into one of misery.
You got another one wrong, Jojo.
Look at Dio.
20 out of 20.
Not a single mistake.
Jojo, your table manners
are simply abhorrent.
You act as if you were raised in a bar.
Clear Jojo's plate at once.
He's had enough. What?
That's all the dinner you get tonight.
It's clear to me that I failed in
your upbringing when I look at Dio.
If your mother could see you now.
Dio's manners are impeccable.
What an oaf.
Our first Fugilist up is Jonathan Joestar.
He's been looking
stronger lately, I'd say.
As for his opponent today, it's
a boxer we haven't seen before.
He's a newcomer to our fair city.
All we know is his name.
It can't be.
Introducing our surprise
opponent, Dio Brando.
Same as ever, land a hit to the other
guy's face and the match is over.
Now fight!
Look at him, dojo tits!
I've never seen the like!
I can't connect!
The pampered brat can box,
I'll grant him that much.
However...
He's never had to punch his way
out of a scrape in the slums,
and thus I hold the advantage.
Take this!
There it is!
Jojo loses the fight!
Your suffering isn't over yet, Jojo.
I'll jam a thumb into
your eye for good measure,
lest you forget who you're dealing with!
That arm of his is unreal.
Dio, that punch was simply amazing!
How did you dodge him so well?
It's just a little defensive
footwork I acquired along the way.
If you'd like to learn it, I'd be more
than happy to teach it to you fellas!
You would do that.
Do take care that nobody shows it to Jojo.
He can't keep a secret to save his life!
You don't say.
Thanks for the warning.
The thumb in my eye.
That was on purpose.
Loneliness will devour a man from within.
I'll reduce Jojo to an empty husk.
Bit by devious bit, I'll steal
the life he was meant to have.
By the time we're grown,
there'll be nothing left of him.
Damn that Dio.
It's terrible.
He's ruining everything he touches.
Look alive, fellas.
Hey, it's me, Jonathan.
What are you doing?
Mind if I join you?
Huh.
I could have sworn I heard
a voice a moment ago.
Just a snitch.
Better to ignore him.
What did you say?
I'm a snitch, huh?
Call me that to my face. Time to go.
You're just nothing but a snitch.
Do you always write about you?
You're just a stupid rich boy, Tattletail.
Tell me what I snitched about then!
He's lying to you!
Why do you just take him at his word?
JoJo the Squealer!
Dio!
He's slandering me!
He lies and lies and
people just eat it up!
From the first day he showed up,
he's been trying to destroy me!
Damn you, Dio Brando!
Dio! Dio! Dio! Dio! No!
Ever since he arrived,
everyone's turned on me.
Even father.
Oh, Danny.
I know you will always be my
friend, no matter what Dio does.
Huh?
Who was that girl just now?
I feel as though I have
seen her face before.
That's my handkerchief.
She brought grapes.
Hey, thank you for the fruit.
You know, I'll be here tomorrow
if you want to come back.
Didn't even tell me her name.
Just ran away.
Girls are such a curious bunch.
A dark time in Jonathan's life was suddenly
made brighter by love's growing embers.
The two became fast friends, and
Jonathan was enchanted by her.
Iran Pendleton, the name
is music to my ears.
She's an angel.
What on earth are you
doing to that poor tree?
Jojo, what possessed you
to do that? Goodness.
Farewell, Iran. Till next time.
Your name wouldn't happen
to be Iran, would it?
You and Jojo, you make such
a smart-looking couple.
Really, I should have guessed as much.
Try as I might to ruin his life,
young Master Jonathan has
been oddly happy as of late.
He?
He did it!
Give her the what for?
The trouble I'd get into
if I was brave as Dio.
He just does what he wants.
Devil may care.
Tell me, have you and Jojo kissed yet?
I'll take that as a no.
You thought your first kiss
would be Jojo, but it was I, Dio.
Even though it was by force, the
fact that I kissed her is enough.
I've killed their romance before it began!
I'll deny Jojo the comfort
of friendship and love.
What the?
Just look at her, Dio She's
taking leave of her senses
What's wrong with her?
That's disgusting Washing
out her mouth with
a muddy puddle Why would anybody do that?
There's a stream not far away
You ungrateful wench!
You dare suggest my kiss is
something to be washed off!
Cool your temper, you damnable fool.
She's not worth losing your head over.
We're done here. Come on.
Arena! Hey there!
Arena, wait!
Why'd she run off?
Was it something I said?
Look at him, fellas.
He doesn't know why she ran away.
What do you say we tell him?
He deserves to know what his
precious arena's been up to.
I don't know.
I'd feel bad making his
little lordship start to cry.
This is his doing.
What have you done, Dio?
What have you done to my arena?
RAAAGH!
DIO!
Hush, boy!
You won't speak my name in vain again
if you know what's good for you.
We end this now!
I won't let you sully an
innocent maiden's honor!
Your fight is with me, dammit!
Upset about Iran?
That she shared her favors with me?
And now you intend to give me a
proper thrashing for my impudence?
This time, Dio, you have gone too far!
You may be right, but
you're the one who'll pay...
Looking to repeat your
performance from our boxing match?
Be my guest.
I can't beat him.
But if I lose here now, I'll spend the
rest of my life cowering in Dio's shadow.
Most of all, I have to
fight for Irina's honor.
She needs a champion!
Time to end this little pissing match.
I'll beat him here, in his own home.
Once and for all, he'll know his proper
place in this world is under my heel.
He'll see that it's useless
to try and defeat me.
I shall be master, now and always.
Come on!
Perfect!
Right in the face!
How are you able to grab me
after such a blow to the head?
Perhaps I was too gentle with you!
Dio!
Impossible!
I'm going to beat you till
you cry like a baby, Dio!
How could a pampered brat
like him best me in a fight?
You how how dare you bastard
how dare you strike me
Days crying i'll make you
regret that you Filthy car stop
it both of you that is
quite enough father i son i
know that boys your age are
prone to fisticuffs however
jojo i saw you pummeled
Dio mercilessly after the
point at which he had obviously
no chance of winning the
fight such is the mark of
a coward no excuses to your
chambers both of you i'll
decide your punishment anon
that seems strange wonder what's in there?
Ah, well.
Probably some are made for out.
What's that?
Something got into the incinerator!
Oh, mercy!
What if a person's in there?
They're burning alive, and it's
all my fault for lighting it!
Iran?
Damn you, Dio!
I beat you fair and square!
But what does it matter if you've
ruined things for Iran and me?
We buried him while you were gone, son.
It was nothing you should have to witness.
The constable said it
was probably the work of
a burglar who caught sight
of Dany and panicked.
Dio, he's not here.
He hasn't yet returned
from school today, sir.
Jojo fled to his room and
fell into a dreamless slumber.
When he awoke, he thought of Danny,
his loyal pet and one true
friend, now lost to him, and wept.
Yes,
I may have evened the
score by killing his mutt,
but it doesn't change the fact that
Jojo is far stronger than I'd thought.
Bloody his nose, and he
comes back twice as fierce.
My anger makes me vulnerable.
I must remedy that.
Once I learn to master my temper, I'll
be invincible to the likes of Jojo.
In the blink of an eye,
seven years passed.
I'll be the roundabout.
The words will make you out and out.
And spend the day your way.
Call it morning, driving through the sun.
And in and out the valley.
The music, dance and sing.
They make the children really ring.
I'll spend the day your way.
Call it morning, driving through the sun.
And in and out the valley.
In and out around the lake.
Miles come out of the sky.
And they'll stand there.
One mile over, we'll be
there and we'll see you.
Ten and two summers, we'll
be there and laughing too.
Twenty-four and five
mile over, we'll see you.
I'll be there with you.
Seven years later...
The bowl is plucked out
of the air by our hero!
Having read it, all has been made clear.
If you're looking to lose
body parts, do stick around.
We are friends no more!
You heard father.
Never again, Dio!